<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<knowl mode="exercise" xmlns="https://spatext.clontz.org" version="0.2">
    <intro>
    <p><em>Scenario:</em></p>
    <p>
        In March 2025, a national education nonprofit surveyed college faculty about the role of AI in the classroom. The survey was conducted in English and {{lanuage}}. To conduct the survey, the nonprofit created a website.  The nonprofit promoted the availability of the survey on social media, emailed faculty directly to invite them to respond, and also asked faculty to forward the survey to their colleagues. Interested faculty could go to the website, enter an email address ending in .edu and upload a picture of their faculty ID card to validate them as college faculty members and then answer the survey. </p>
    <p>
        850 faculty responded to the survey. Respondents were asked to what degree they agreed with the following, using a 5-point scale: “Strongly Agree,” “Agree,” “Neutral,” “Disagree,” or “Strongly Disagree.””</p>
    
        <list>
            <item><p>Out-of-touch professors should harshly crack down on lazy students using AI to cheat on their assignments by completely banning it in their rigorous classes, if they want students to learn anything.</p></item>
            <item><p>Complacent and profit-driven universities are turning a blind eye to the out-of-control misuse of AI by students, doing almost nothing to address the crisis.</p></item>
        </list>
    <p>
        <m>{{result_1}}\%</m> survey respondents said that they {{agree_1}} with the statement "Out-of-touch professors should harshly crack down on lazy students using AI to cheat on their assignments by completely banning it in their rigorous classes, if they want students to learn anything." <m>{{result_2}}\%</m> said that they {{agree_2}} with the statement "Complacent and profit-driven universities are turning a blind eye to the out-of-control misuse of AI by students, doing almost nothing to address the crisis".</p>
        
    </intro>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>Does the above use a sampling frame? If so, what is the sampling frame?</p></content>
        <outtro><p>No, there was no sample frame used</p></outtro>
    </knowl>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>What is the sampling method used in the above scenario?</p></content>
        <outtro><p>The sampling method was a voluntary response, explanation needed</p></outtro>
    </knowl>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>Looking at the sampling frame and the sampling method, would the sample be a valid sample or is it likely to be a biased sample? Explain why.</p></content>
        <outtro><p>The sampling method is bias, so the sample is bias. Student's need to explain why the sampling method is bias</p></outtro>
    </knowl>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>Identify potential sources of bias other than the sampling method and sampling frame from the information given and explain why they lead to bias (Only use the information given, do not speculate about information not provided).</p></content>
        <outtro><p>Only limited language choices; the wording of the statements. Explanations needed.</p></outtro></knowl>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>If they did the survey again, would you expect that exactly <m>{{result_2}}\%</m> of respondents would {{agree_2}} with the statement "Overreaching states should not have the unchecked authority to impose extreme bans on widely used and medically approved abortion drugs under the guise of protecting life."? Why or why not?</p></content>
        <outtro><p>No, the exact same result would not be expected due to sampling variability, explanation needed</p></outtro>
    </knowl>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>Based on the results of this survey, can the national education nonprofit be sure they have a good idea of how college faculty members feel about the role of AI in the classroom? Why or why not?</p></content>
        <outtro><p>No, too much bias, explanation needed. </p></outtro></knowl>
</knowl>
