<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<knowl mode="exercise" xmlns="https://spatext.clontz.org" version="0.2">
    <intro>
    <p><em>Scenario:</em></p>
    <p>
        In Summer 2025, a medical research nonprofit randomly surveyed 1,100 registered voters in {{state_1}} and {{state_2}} about proposed restrictions on access to medication abortion (like mifepristone). The survey was conducted in English and {{language}}.</p>
    <p>
        Survey respondents were asked to what degree they agreed with the following statements, using a 5-point scale: “Strongly Agree,” “Agree,” “Neutral,” “Disagree,” or “Strongly Disagree.”</p>
    
        <list>
            <item><p>The unaccountable FDA should not be allowed to recklessly and irresponsibly expand access to abortion pills through unregulated telehealth schemes without meaningful oversight.</p></item>
            <item><p>Overreaching states should not have the unchecked authority to impose extreme bans on widely used and medically approved abortion drugs under the guise of protecting life.</p></item>
        </list>
    <p>
        <m>{{result_1}}\%</m> survey respondents said that they {{agree_1}} with the statement "The unaccountable FDA should not be allowed to recklessly and irresponsibly expand access to abortion pills through unregulated telehealth schemes without meaningful oversight." <m>{{result_2}}\%</m> said that they {{agree_2}} with the statement "Overreaching states should not have the unchecked authority to impose extreme bans on widely used and medically approved abortion drugs under the guise of protecting life".</p>
        
    </intro>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>Does the above use a sampling frame? If so, what is the sampling frame?</p></content>
        <outtro><p>Yes, there is a sampling frame in this scenario. The frame is registered voter in {{state_1}} and {{state_2}}</p></outtro>
    </knowl>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>What is the sampling method used in the above scenario?</p></content>
        <outtro><p>The sampling method was a SRS, explanation needed</p></outtro>
    </knowl>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>Looking at the sampling frame and the sampling method, would the sample be a valid sample or is it likely to be a biased sample? Explain why.</p></content>
        <outtro><p>The sampling method is valid. The sampling frame is NOT valid so the sample is bias. Student's need to explain why the sampling frame is bias</p></outtro>
    </knowl>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>Identify potential sources of bias other than the sampling method and sampling frame from the information given and explain why they lead to bias (Only use the information given, do not speculate about information not provided).</p></content>
        <outtro><p>Only limited language choices; the wording of the statements. Explanations needed.</p></outtro></knowl>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>If they did the survey again, would you expect that exactly <m>{{result_2}}</m><m>\%</m> of respondents would {{agree_2}} with the statement "Overreaching states should not have the unchecked authority to impose extreme bans on widely used and medically approved abortion drugs under the guise of protecting life."? Why or why not?</p></content>
        <outtro><p>No, the exact same result would not be expected due to sampling variability, explanation needed</p></outtro>
    </knowl>
    <knowl>
        <content><p>Based on the results of this survey, can the medical research nonprofit be sure they have a good idea of how Americans feel about proposed restrictions on access to medication abortion (like mifepristone)? Why or why not?</p></content>
        <outtro><p>No, too much bias, explanation needed. </p></outtro></knowl>
</knowl>
